Now that we've learned a bit about the importance of categorical variables,
现在我们已经知道了分类变量的重要性
how about we go back to all tricks to view how to actually analyze them.
我们回顾一下刚刚使用的技巧 看看如何实际分析数据
What we can use is the frequency tool with our cleaned up data to
我们可以在清洗过的数据中使用 frequency (频率) 工具
take a look at our target field, churn, since it is a categorical variable.
先查看目标字段 churn 因为它是一个分类变量
First thing we should do is just grab that cleaned up data set.
我们要做的第一件事是打开清洗过的数据集
So we're going to use an input data tool to go grab it.
所以使用 input (输入) 工具打开数据集
The drop down menu, and then churn data, cleaned.
在下拉列表中选择 churn data cleaned 文件
The next thing I want to do, is go back to my data investigation category and
接下来我要做的是 返回 data investigation (数据导航) 界面
grab this frequency table tool.
拖拽 frequency table tool (频率表工具)
Inside of this, we can ask to get a frequency result from
在这个工具中 我们可以得到
all of our different categorical string variables.
所有不同类型的字符串变量的频率结果
What I'm going to choose.
我现在选择的
Is just that one churn field.
只有 churn 一个字段
And then I'm going to bring in a browse after our interactive output,
接着我拖拽 browse (浏览) 到交互输出结果
then hit run to run this analysis.
然后点击 run 去运行这个分析
One of the first things I want to know about my different categorical
我想要知道的第一件事是
variables, is how many unique groups it has within it.
分类变量内部有多少唯一的组
In this case since this churn field is a binary field, it's a true or
在这个案例中 churn 字段是一个二进制字段 它只有 true
a false, clearly we have two different unique options, true And false.
或者 false 很显然我们只有 2 个不同的唯一选项 true 和 false
Then the next thing I look for is that frequency and the percentage
接下来我要查看的是这个单独变量中
of our different categories within this individual variable.
不同类型的频数和百分比
And it definitely looks that we have way more false values than our true values.
很明显 看起来假值的数量大于真值的数量
It seems that we actually have about 86% false values and about 14% true values.
看起来 我们实际有约 86% 的假值和约 14% 的真值
And if we go to the frequency,
如果我们转到 frequency (频数)
we're able to see that we have 4,200 false values and 700 true values.
我们可以看到有 4200 假值和 700 真值
What I get from this result is, that since there's so
从这个结果能够看出
many more false values than true values
因为假值的数量远大于真值的数量
It may actually be difficult to predict just a few number of records.
所以可能很难去进行预测 因为只有这一点记录
If this is something that does seem actually logical in the large scheme of
如果这是一个发生在大规模项目中的数据 也是有可能合乎逻辑
things, more customers are going to stay with their cell phone carrier
比如 更多的客户会一直选择使用一家手机运营商
than actually churn over and go to another carrier.
而不是转到另一家运营商
But, what I wanted to show you is,
但是 我想要告诉你的是
how you actually analyzed your different categorical variables within Alteryx,
如何使用 Alteryx 实际分析不同的分类变量
and, hopefully, you're able to see how easy it is to perform this analysis, by,
希望你能够看到进行分析是多么地简单
simply, just bringing in a frequency table tool.
只需要简单地拖拽一个 frequency table tool (频率表工具)